<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Me on Namratha Vasu</title>
    <link>https://vasunam.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Me on Namratha Vasu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vasunam.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Udio&#39;s Onboarding Flow: Hitting the Right Notes (and Missing a Few)</title>
      <link>https://vasunam.github.io/posts/udios-onboarding-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vasunam.github.io/posts/udios-onboarding-flow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently took Udio—a promising new music-generation app—for a spin, and it quickly reminded me just how crucial first impressions are in shaping a user&amp;rsquo;s experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Right away, Udio greets you with a clean, familiar login screen: &amp;ldquo;Sign up for free to continue,&amp;rdquo; with the usual suspects like Google, Apple, and Discord waiting to authenticate you. On the right side of the screen, there&amp;rsquo;s a fun little teaser: &amp;ldquo;A song about logging into Udio is loading&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;. Clever and playful—except that the song never actually loaded. Not exactly the smooth start I was hoping for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Compose</title>
      <link>https://vasunam.github.io/great-ideas/smart-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vasunam.github.io/great-ideas/smart-compose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;smart-compose-evolution-of-an-ai-writing-assistant&#34;&gt;Smart Compose: Evolution of an AI Writing Assistant&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gmail&amp;rsquo;s Smart Compose feature represents a fascinating evolution of AI-assisted writing, progressing from basic predictive text to a sophisticated writing assistant that understands context, style, and intent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This case study examines how the feature evolved through three distinct stages of development, from initial concept to fully realized product feature.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories Feature</title>
      <link>https://vasunam.github.io/great-ideas/stories-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vasunam.github.io/great-ideas/stories-feature/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stories-feature-from-ephemeral-sharing-to-platform-standard&#34;&gt;Stories Feature: From Ephemeral Sharing to Platform Standard&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instagram&amp;rsquo;s Stories feature represents one of the most influential product innovations in social media, transforming how users share and consume content across platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This case study examines how the feature evolved from a simple concept borrowed from Snapchat into a platform-defining format that has been adopted across the social media landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
